Guide to the War Poster Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- World War I, 1914-1918; Series I
  - Yale University Library Collection
    - United States of America
      - Stamp it out. Buy War Savings Stamps. McGill, T.D., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0462; 14x18 inches (Box 180)
        Artist: McGill, T.D.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Make Good the Promise. Over Here, Over There. Second War Fund., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0463; 17x02 inches (Box 180)
      - Make Good the Promise. Over Here, Over There. Second War Fund., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0464; 55x35 inches (Box 180)
      - Buy China Life Saving Stamps, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0465; 15x20 inches (Box 180)
        Artist: McNulty, William C.. Place of Publication: United States.
      - Save a life in China - millions starving - China Famine Fund., 1920; YUS0466; 21x30 inches (Box 180)
      - Boost! Boy Scout Week., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0467; 21x25 inches (Box 180)
      - From Service to Service. Your Church Calls You., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0468; 22x31 inches (Box 180)
      - What Shall We Make of Him? Methodist Centenary., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0469; 19x28 inches (Box 180)
        Artist: Neill. Place of Publication: United States.
      - A Madonna of the Ganges. Methodist Centenary., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0470; 19x29 inches (Box 180)
      - You Are Wanted By The U.S. Army, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YUS0471; 29x42 inches (Box 180)
        Artist: Bara, K.M.. Place of Publication: United States.
    - Canada
      - Send More Men. Won't YOU Answer the Call?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YCA0001; 25x38 inches (Box 181)
      - Here's Your Chance. It's Men We Want., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YCA0002; 25x38 inches (Box 181)
      - You are no exception. Join Now., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YCA0003; 25x38 inches (Box 181)
      - If ye Break faith - we shall not sleep. Buy Victory Bonds., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YCA0004; 35x24 inches (Box 181)
      - Victory Bonds Will Help Stop This - Kultur vs. Humanity., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YCA0005; 24x36 inches (Box 181)
      - Doing My Bit Four Years. Do Yours. Buy Victory Bonds., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YCA0006; 24x36 inches (Box 181)
      - Back Him Up! Buy Victory Bonds., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YCA0007; 24x36 inches (Box 181)
      - They serve France. How can I serve Canada? Buy Victory Bonds., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YCA0008; 24x35 inches (Box 181)
      - Yours not to do and die - Yours but to go and Buy Victory Bonds., 1918; YCA0009; 24x36 inches (Box 181)
      - To Maintain the Prosperity of Canada. Buy Victory Bonds, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YCA0010; 24x36 inches (Box 181)
      - Keep All Canadians Busy. Buy 1918 Victory Bonds., YCA0011; 18x24 inches (Box 181)
      - 4 Reasons for buying Victory Bonds., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YCA0012; 18x24 inches (Box 181)
    - France
      - Oeuvre du Recondort du Soldat., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YFR0001; 11x15 inches (Box 182)
      - Matinee au profit des artistes russes residant en France, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YFR0002; 32x47 inches (Box 182)
        Artist: Stelletski, D.. Place of Publication: France.
      - Pour le triomphe souscrivez a l'emprunt national...Banque National, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YFR0003; 31x45 inches (Box 182)
        Artist: Sem. Place of Publication: France.
      - Untitled, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YFR0004; 48x31 inches (Box 182)
      - Carte Symbolique de l'Europe. Guerre Liberatrice 1914-1915., 1914 November; YFR0005; 26x20 inches (Box 182)
        Artist: Cretee, B.. Place of Publication: France.
      - Carte Symbolique de l'Europe. Guerre Liberatrice 1914-1915., 1914 November; YFR0006; 26x20 inches (Box 182)
      - Tehatre de la Guerre Europeene. 1914-1915., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YFR0007; 25x21 inches (Box 182)
        Artist: Huguenin, Andre.. Place of Publication: France.
      - Untitled, 1915; YFR0008; 31x39 inches (Box 182)
      - Pour la belle terre de France., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YFR0009; 20x15 inches (Box 182)
      - Les vainqueurs de la Marne., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YFR0010; 20x21 inches (Box 182)
    - Great Britain
      - Transport Economy...Board of Trade. Ministry of Food., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YGB0001; 14x17 inches (Box 183)
      - Untitled, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YGB0002; 99x99 inches (Box 183)
      - Landless. Published by the Labour Party., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YGB0003; 30x40 inches (Box 183)
      - Men of London! Remember, We must have more men, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YGB0004; 14x17 inches (Box 183)
      - British Subjects. It is your duty to enlist, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YGB0005; 21x24 inches (Box 183)
    - Germany
      - Aufruf der Volksregierung, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YGE0001; 18x23 inches (Box 184)
      - Kaiser Wilhelms Rede an sein Ostheer...Der Geist des Herrn ist, 1914 December; YGE0002; 25x19 inches (Box 184)
      - Befehl. Gemass Verordnungsblatt Nr. 140, 1919 June 18; YGE0003; 24x18 inches (Box 184)
      - Zeichnet Achte Kriegsanleihe., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YGE0004; 32x22 inches (Box 184)
        Artist: Lenz, M.. Place of Publication: Germany.
      - Ersatzmittelausstellung (E.M.A.) Grupe. Papiergewebe., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YGE0005; 39x50 inches (Box 184)
        Artist: Biro. Place of Publication: Germany.
      - 8 Zeichnet Kriegsanleihe., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YGE0006; 37x50 inches (Box 184)
        Artist: R.K.. Place of Publication: Germany.
      - Seerarber Bund Stortebeker, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YGE0007; 22x30 inches (Box 184)
    - Czechoslovakia
      - Stedre Dni...Ceskkoslovenskeho Cerveneho Kriza., 1919 March 25-30; YCZ0001; 25x37 inches (Box 185)
        Artist: Hrska. Place of Publication: Czechoslovakia.
    - Holland
      - (Stamps), Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YHO0001; 12x14 inches (Box 185)
        Artist: Unknown. Place of Publication: Holland. Several Sheets.
    - Italy
      - Untitled, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YIT0001; 99x99 inches (Box 185)
      - Finalmente!!, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YIT0002; 35x26 inches (Box 185)
    - Mexico
      - V. Consejo Obrero Nacional., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; YMX0001; 27x37 inches (Box 185)
        Artist: Epperan. Place of Publication: Mexico.
    - Switzerland
      - Schweizer-Schritten-Schritten-Fremde...Freiheit und Frieden, 1915; YSW0001; 13x18 inches (Box 185)
        Artist: R.M.. Place of Publication: Switzerland.
  - Simon Brett Collection
    - Search Your Fruit Trees for the Oriental Peach Moth, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Answer the Red Cross Christmas Roll Call, 1918 (Box 186)
    - Answer the Red Cross Christmas Roll Call, 1918 (Box 186)
    - Raise More Poultry, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Women of Connecticut are you Helping?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Save Seed for Victory, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Do Your Duty. Join the U.S. Marines, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Your President and Your Governor Endorse the Children's Year, 1918 (Box 186)
    - Send Sammy Smilage, $1.00, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Send Sammy Smilage, $1.00, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Send Sammy Smilage, $1.00, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Would Nathan Hale Hold Back If He Were Here Today?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Boys and Girls! A Million Dollars Worth of Food Has Been Set As The Goal For The Junior Food Army, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Search Your Fruit Trees for the Oriental Peach Moth, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Do Not Sell Laying Hens, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - President Wilson to the People of the United States, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Remember! The Flag of Liberty, Support It!, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Save Seed for Victory, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Boys and Girls! A Million Dollars Worth of Food Has Been Set As The Goal For The Junior Food Army, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - New England's Liberty Loan Record, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - E-E-E-Yah-Yip. Go Over With U.S. Marines, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Free Storage of Liberty Bonds, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Garden Plant-lice or Aphids, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Buy Early, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Buy Early, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Joan of Arc Saved France. Women of America, Save Your Country, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Serg't Ruth Farnam. First American Woman Soldier, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - He Did His Duty. Will You?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Have You a Red Cross Service Flag?, 1918 (Box 186)
    - Make good the promise, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Buy Liberty Bonds. "That Government of the People...", Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Hun or Home? Buy More Liberty Bonds., Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Clear-The-Way-!! Buy Bonds. Fourth Liberty Loan., Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - The Ships are Coming, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Come On! Buy More Liberty Bonds, 1918 (Box 186)
    - Remember Belgium. Buy Bonds Fourth Liberty Loan., Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Have You a Red Cross Service Flag?, 1918 (Box 186)
    - To-day Buy That Liberty Bond, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - E-E-E-Yah-Yip. Go Over With U.S. Marines, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - The Greatest Mother in the World, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
      Artist: Foringer, A.E.. Place of Publication: United States.
    - USA Bonds. Third Liberty Loan Campaign, Boy Scouts of America, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - I Am Telling You, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - They Give Their Lives. Do You Lend Your Savings?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Buy A Bond of the 2nd Liberty Loan and Help Win the War, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Buy To-day. Buy Liberty Bonds at Any Bank, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
      Artist: Bush, S.L.. Place of Publication: United States.
    - Ring it Again. Buy U.S.GOV'T Bonds, Third Liberty Loan, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Beat Back the Hun with Liberty Bonds, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Teufel Hunden. German Nickname for U.S. Marines. Devil Dog Recruiting Station, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Keep Him Free. Buy War Savings Stamps, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Boys and Girls! You Can Help Your Uncle Sam Win the War, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Our Daddy Is Fighting at the Front for You, 1917 (Box 186)
    - What the Navy is Doing. Athletics Fit Men to Win, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - What the Navy is Doing. Downing the Hun Submarine, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Women of Connecticut are you Helping?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - What the Navy is Doing. Downing the Hun Submarine, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - What the Navy is Doing. The Road to France - The Navy Keeps it Open, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - What the Navy is Doing. Convoying in Winter, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - What the Navy is Doing. Athletics Fit Men to Win, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - What the Navy is Doing. Convoying in Winter, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Life in the Navy. Food for Fighters, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - My Patriotic Duty is Red Cross Work, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Get Smileage Books Inside, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - My Soldier, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - A Good Part of the Proceeds of this Farm Have Gone into Liberty, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Tired of Giving? You Don't Know What it is to be Tired!, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
      Artist: Ding, J.N.. Place of Publication: United States.
    - My Soldier, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - E-E-E-Yah-Yip. Go Over With U.S. Marines, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - The Red Cross Needs You, Join Now, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - Raise More Poultry, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 186)
    - On the Job For Victory, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 187)
    - Be a U.S. Marine!, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 187)
    - If You Want to Fight, Join the Marines., 1915 (Box 187)
    - Tell That to the Marines, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 187)
    - The Hun - his Mark. Blot it Out with Liberty Bonds., Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 187)
    - Sure! We'll Finish the Job. Victory Liberty Loan., 1918 (Box 187)
    - That Liberty Shall Not Perish from the Earth Buy Liberty Bonds, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 187)
    - Keep These Off the U.S.A. Buy More Liberty Bonds, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 187)
    - Must Children Die and Mothers Plead in Vain?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 187)
    - U.S. Marines. "Soldiers of the Sea", Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 187)
    - U.S. Marines. "Soldiers of the Sea", Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 187)
    - This Device on Hat or Helmet Means U.S. Marines, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 187)
    - I Want You for the Navy, 1917 (Box 187)
    - Have You Answered the Red Cross Christmas Roll Call?, 1918 (Box 187)
    - Have You Answered the Red Cross Christmas Roll Call?, 1918 (Box 187)
    - Tell That to the Marines At 19 Congress Street, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 187)
    - Tell That to the Marines At 19 Congress Street, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 187)
    - The Hun - his Mark. Blot it Out with Liberty Bonds., Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 187)
    - What Are You Doing To Help?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 187)
    - U.S. Marines. "Soldiers of the Sea", Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 187)
    - U.S. Marine. Be a Sea Soldier, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 187)
    - Another Notch Chateau Thierry. U.S. Marines., Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 187)
    - I Want You for the Navy, 1917 (Box 187)
    - Join the Navy. The Service for Fighting Men, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 187)
    - Tell That to the Marines At 19 Congress Street, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 187)
    - This Device on Hat or Helmet Means U.S. Marines, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 187)
    - Joan of Arc Saved France. Women of America, Save Your Country, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 187)
    - My Soldier. Buy United States Government Bonds, Third Liberty Loan, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 187)
  - Paul Jean Gaxton Darrott Collection
    - Sauvons les Bebes Par L'allaitement Maternel, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 188)
      Artist: Stephany, R.. Place of Publication: France.
    - Deux Coeurs Fideles qui Ont Souffert sous la Jouq Allemand et esperent la delivrance Francaise!, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 188)
      Artist: Levy, D.. Place of Publication: France.
    - Souscrivez au Iveme. Emprunt et le Drapeau Tricolore, 1918 (Box 188)
    - Pour Que Vos Enfants Ne Connaissent Plus Les Horreurs de la Guerre, Souscrivez A l'Emprunt National Societe Generale, 1917 (Box 188)
      Artist: Reson, Georges. Place of Publication: France.
    - Champ de Bataille de l'Ourcq, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 188)
      Artist: Unknown. Place of Publication: France. Map.
    - France: Division Administrative, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 188)
    - Share. Jewish Relief Campaign, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 189)
      Artist: Burke. Place of Publication: United States.
    - Czechoslovaks! Join Our Free Colors!, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 189)
    - Untitled, 1918 (Box 189)
      Artist: Bracker, M. Leone. Place of Publication: United States. Depiction of three servicemen.
    - That Liberty Shall Not Perish from the Earth Buy Liberty Bonds, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 189)
    - War Gardens Victorious, 1919 (Box 189)
    - Feed a Fighter, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 189)
      Artist: Morgan, W.. Place of Publication: United States.
    - War Gardens over the Top, 1919 (Box 189)
    - Lest We Perish...American Committee for Relief in the Near East, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 189)
    - 3,500,000 of us are Starving in Europe. Help Us., Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 189)
      Artist: Emmons, Marion. Place of Publication: United States.
  - Charles Whittelsey Collection
    - Austria
      - 6 Kriegsanleihe! 10 Mai bis 8., 1917 May 10-June 8; WAU0001 (Box 190)
        Artist: Jachauer. Place of Publication: Austria.
    - Belgium
      - Salon anti-boche, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WBE0001 (Box 190)
        Artist: Unknown. Place of Publication: Belgium.
    - France
      - Il Avance L'Heure de la Victoire., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WFR0001 (Box 190)
    - Great Britain
      - Guild of Play, 1917; WGB0001 (Box 190)
        Artist: Kruger, George. Place of Publication: Great Britain.
    - Holland
      - Elk mud koren...200 Menchen van een pond brood!, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WHO0001 (Box 191)
        Artist: Stuiten, Willy. Place of Publication: Holland.
    - East Indies
      - [East Indian], 1918; WIN0001 (Box 191)
        Artist: Evans, B.J.. Place of Publication: East Indies.
    - Italy
      - Per la patria...Per la pace...Prestito Nazionale, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WIT0001 (Box 191)
      - Prestito Nazionale 5%, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WIT0002 (Box 191)
      - Prestito Nazionale, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WIT0003 (Box 191)
    - Russia
      - [Russian], Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WRU0001 (Box 191)
      - [Russian], Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WRU0002 (Box 191)
    - Switzerland
      - Dono Nazionale Svizzero, 1918; WSW0001 (Box 191)
        Artist: Courvoisier, J.. Place of Publication: Switzerland.
    - Germany
      - Zeichne die Kriegsanleihe! Seer und Flotte erwarten es von Dir!, 1917; WGE0001 (Box 192)
        Artist: Bernhard. Place of Publication: Germany.
      - Bleibt einig!, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WGE0002 (Box 192)
      - Fur die kriegsanleihe!, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WGE0003 (Box 192)
        Artist: Plontka. Place of Publication: Germany.
      - Kanin-felle abliefern!, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WGE0004 (Box 192)
        Artist: Gipkens, Julius. Place of Publication: Germany.
      - Zeichnet Kriegsanleihe! Fur einen guten frieden!, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WGE0005 (Box 192)
        Artist: Dettman. Place of Publication: Germany.
      - Gold Gab Ich zur Wehr. Eisen Nahm Ich zur Ehr., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WGE0006 (Box 192)
      - Zeichnet Kriegsanleihe., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WGE0007 (Box 192)
        Artist: Sigrist, K.. Place of Publication: Germany.
      - Und Eure Pflicht? Zeichnet kriegsanleihe., 1918; WGE0008 (Box 192)
        Artist: Horrmeyer. Place of Publication: Germany.
      - Erwigt nicht die junge Freiheit durch Unordnung und Brudermord, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WGE0009 (Box 192)
      - Mutter! Denk an mich! Wahle Sozialdemokratisch!, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WGE0010 (Box 192)
        Artist: Kirchbach. Place of Publication: Germany.
      - Freiheit, Friede, Arbeit. Wahlt die Deutsche Volkspartei, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WGE0011 (Box 192)
      - Madchen u. Frauen heraus aus der Finsternis!, 1919; WGE0012 (Box 192)
        Artist: Kainer. Place of Publication: Germany.
      - Deutschnationale Volkspartei...Wahlt Deutsch-National., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WGE0013 (Box 192)
        Artist: Gross, M.. Place of Publication: Germany.
      - Die rote Fahne, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WGE0014 (Box 192)
      - Soll diese Elend weiter gehen?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WGE0015 (Box 192)
      - Die Heimat ist in gefahr!, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WGE0016 (Box 193)
        Artist: Hacherz. Place of Publication: Germany.
      - Agir. Ein Film-Festspiel., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WGE0017 (Box 193)
        Artist: Oppenheim, Louis. Place of Publication: Germany.
      - Wir wollen leben. Zeichnet Kriegsanleihe., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WGE0018 (Box 193)
        Artist: Sigrist. Place of Publication: Germany.
      - Und Du? Liste Luppe., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WGE0019 (Box 193)
      - Freiwillige bor! Es gilt den Erhutz unserer Ostgrenze!, 1919; WGE0020 (Box 193)
        Artist: Cay. Place of Publication: Germany.
      - Bei Deutschland davemder Wohlstand, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WGE0021 (Box 193)
      - Nieder mit dem Bolschewismus, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WGE0022 (Box 193)
      - Elend und Untergang folgen der Anarchie., 1918; WGE0023 (Box 193)
        Artist: Engelhard. Place of Publication: Germany.
      - Berliner. Schutzt euer eignenes Heim!, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WGE0024 (Box 193)
      - Halt, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WGE0025 (Box 193)
      - Zaudert nicht sondern meldet Euch, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WGE0026 (Box 193)
      - Bildet deutsche Volksrate, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WGE0027 (Box 193)
      - Der Rechtsfriede Bringt den Volkerfruhling., 1919 May 1; WGE0028 (Box 193)
        Artist: Freyberg. Place of Publication: Germany.
      - Alle Stimmen fur das Hochste Menschheitziel: den Sozialismus., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; WGE0029 (Box 193)
        Artist: Kress, Will. Place of Publication: Germany.
  - William Mullally Collection
    Existence and Location of Copies
    Available in microfilm - HM 157 (2 reels, 35mm).
    - I Summon you to Comradeship in the Red Cross, 1918 (Box 194)
    - Have You Answered the Red Cross Christmas Roll Call?, 1918 (Box 194)
    - They Shall Not Perish...American Committee for Relief in the, 1918 (Box 194)
      Artist: Volk, Douglas. Place of Publication: United States.
    - Lest They Perish … American Committee for Relief in the Near East, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 194)
    - The Child at Your Door. American Committee Relief in the Near, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 194)
    - Lest We Perish...American Committee for Relief in the Near East, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 194)
    - Give or We Perish. American Committee for Relief in the Near East., Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 194)
    - How Much Will You Lend to the Boys Who Are Giving All, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 194)
    - Help Uncle Sam Stamp Out the Kaiser. Buy U.S.Gov't Bonds, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 194)
    - Shall we be More Tender with our Dollars than with the Lives of our Sons, 1917 (Box 194)
    - She Does Not Ask for Contributions. She Asks you to Invest Your Money at 4% in U.S. Government Bonds, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 194)
    - Before Sunset Buy a U.S. Government Bond of the 2nd Liberty Loan of 1917, Circa 1917 (Box 194)
      Artist: De Land, Eugenie. Place of Publication: United States.
    - The $3,000,000,000 Punch., Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 194)
    - Ring it Again. Buy a United States Government Bond of the Second Liberty Loan of 1917, Circa 1917 (Box 194)
    - Feelings of the Man Who Delays Buying His Liberty Bonds., 1917 (Box 194)
    - Second Liberty Loan of 1917, Buy a Bond., Circa 1917 (Box 194)
    - Second Liberty Loan of 1917, Buy a Bond., Circa 1917 (Box 194)
    - Shall We Be More Tender with our Dollars than with the Lives of Our Sons, Circa 1917 (Box 194)
    - By the President of the United States of America, a Proclamation. Wednesday, the 24th of October, as Liberty Day, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 194)
    - Buy Liberty Bonds, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 194)
    - Our Daddy Is Fighting at the Front for You, Circa 1917 (Box 194)
    - Lend Your Money to Your Government, Circa 1917 (Box 194)
    - The Time Has Come to Conquer or Submit., Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 194)
    - Remember Your First Thrill of American Liberty., Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 194)
    - Buy A Liberty Bond of the U.S. Government and Wear this Button - It is a Badge of Honor, Circa 1914 - circa 1918 (Box 194)
    - Women! Help America's Sons Win the War, Circa 1917 (Box 194)
      Artist: Porteus, R.H.. Place of Publication: United States. Booklet "Public - No. 43 - 65th Congress. H.R. 5901." and two Buy Liberty Bond cards attached to backing.
    - Answer the Red Cross Christmas Roll Call, 1918 (Box 195)
    - Red Cross Christmas Roll Call, 1918 (Box 195)